<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tech on Launch Today</title><link>http://komi.dev/categories/tech/</link><description>Recent content in Tech on Launch Today</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://komi.dev/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>const and static in Rust</title><link>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-12-when-to-use-lazy_static/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-12-when-to-use-lazy_static/</guid><description>Global variable in Rust In functional programming, the way to use global variable properly is just to avoid using it. This is not a joke. Modern software engineering requires variables to be scoped, and at the same time, they shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be changed even in scopes such as closures.
However, we can&amp;rsquo;t sometimes avoid using global variable (Somtimes codes can be cleaner.) For such situations, Rust provides some syntax to controll global variables.</description></item><item><title>Modernize Emacs</title><link>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-07-modernize-emacs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-07-modernize-emacs/</guid><description>Do you know Emacs? Today there are many editors. The most popular one seems Visual Stadio Code. Nobody can complain about this fact. And the second one may be Vim. Nobody can also complain about this.
But&amp;hellip;Well&amp;hellip; By the say, do you know Emacs?
Emacs is a kind of editors and has so long history. Today, a few people use this. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why Emacs is not popular because I think this is really customizable and light-weighted.</description></item><item><title>Tools and Ecosystem of WebAssembly with Rust</title><link>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-06-ecosystems-of-wasm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-06-ecosystems-of-wasm/</guid><description>About WebAssembly First of all, you have to understand what WebAssembly is.
Mozilla says &amp;hellip;
WebAssembly is a new type of code that can be run in modern web browsers — it is a low-level assembly-like language with a compact binary format that runs with near-native performance and provides languages such as C/C++, C# and Rust with a compilation target so that they can run on the web. It is also designed to run alongside JavaScript, allowing both to work together.</description></item><item><title>Hello My New Blog</title><link>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-05-make-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://komi.dev/post/2020-09-05-make-blog/</guid><description>About me Hello, my name is Yusuke Kominami. I&amp;rsquo;m living in Japan, and working as a machine learning engineer. I&amp;rsquo;m 23 years old and graguated from Kyoto University in this March. When I was student, I majored in Bioinformatics. Why am I a software engineer? Actually, I&amp;rsquo;m not interested in Biology, more interested in computing. So when I was in university, I just stuck on programming. For more about me,</description></item></channel></rss>